Gary T. Holman

3954 S. 300 East • Anderson, IN 46017 • (269) 484-4331 • gth.softdev@gmail.com

OBJECTIVE

I am a technical specialist seeking an opportunity as Software Developer. While I am new to software development, I have 20+ years of progressive experience in software, programming, design, training and end-user support. I am looking for a work-from-home position that requires a dedicated and experienced individual with exceptional customer service and communication skills.

EDUCATION

New Horizons Computer Learning Center, Carmel, IN • 2009

Credentials: MCP, MCSA and CompTIA Security+

Andrews University, Berrien Springs, MI • 1990

Bachelors Business Administration / Management Information Systems

SKILLS

- Networking/System Admin
- Active Directory
- Labtech Software
- Technical Support
- Customer Service
- Programming/Implementation
- Hardware/Software
- Installation
- Troubleshooting
- Dataserver/Analyzer

- Windows Operating Systems
- Group Policy
- Axcient Certified Expert
- Video/Audio clips
- Communication/teaching
- Director/Authorware/Flash
- Express/Basic/COBOL/DOS/ FORTRAN/UNIX
- Novell
- Tango/RoboHelp

- Dbase/Lotus 1-2-3/FoxPro
- Network Wiring
- Connectwise
- WordPerfect/Word/Excel/Access
 MS PowerPoint
- Adobe PhotoShop/Premiere
- Apple Quick time
- Setup Factory
- Sound Forge/Acid Music
- Technical Writing

PROFESSIONAL EMPLOYMENT

Specified Lighting, Carmel, IN • 2017 - 2020

Controls Specialist

- Responsible for quoting lighting controls for construction projects across Indiana.
- Maintained up-to-date information regarding control equipment/devices from various manufacturers in order to match the proper equipment for the particular job.

Exacq Technologies, Fishers, IN • 2011 - 2017

Tier 2 Technical Support Representative

 Assist customers, dealers, and installers worldwide with issues resulting from use of exacqVision software via phone and e-mail. • Troubleshoot hardware issues with equipment dedicated to exacqVision video management.

Indy Tech Pro, L.L.C, Indianapolis, IN • 2011

Systems Project Leader

- Assisted with server migration.
- Responsible for Labtech Managed Services rollout.
- Managed Axcient backup solutions for business clients.

Axcess PC Consulting, Inc., Indianapolis, IN • 2010 - 2011

Part-Time Systems Technician

- Assisted in Business Client maintenance programs.
- Assisted with residential break/fix issues.
- Assisted with virus/malware removal, data transfers, new PC configurations.

Self Employed/Co-Owner, Anderson, IN • 2003 - 2008

Internet Business

- Involved in all aspects of small business startup from inception.
- Designed, created and maintained website.
- Purchased and modified inventory software, maintained inventory, photographed product and retouched digital photos.
- Created online advertisement and maintained e-commerce for payment systems.

Interactive Learning Systems, Inc., Battle Creek, MI • 1997 - 2003

Technical Specialist/Multimedia Programmer

- Developed numerous help systems, web based training programs and QA.
- Proficient in CBT production that includes all phases of design, programming and implementation.

Information Resources, Inc., • Chicago, IL • 1994-1997

Database Administrator

- Provided on-site help desk support at the Kellogg Company Headquarters, Battle Creek, Michigan.
- Automated database and wrote program queries.
- Analyzed users' needs for specific database programming.